I said gay in a song, now I'm a criminal Try to teach some history, now I'm political They banned my books, burned my words Guess free speech is just for birds Tried to play a show in Tampa Bay But the venue vanished yesterday No dancing here, no drag, no fun Your freedom state just pulled a gun Can't play it in the panhandle No more too loud, too proud, too real, too ignore They locked the answer, boarded the doors
Filed, underworked, and dangerous trash Sing it loud before they smash Your busted boombox of free speech For rental rights or fascist fides One man's fear is another's life They ban what's brown, they ban what's queer They ban whatever they don't wanna hear or state Now say it, now shame your states This window, different plate, what's 18th Street?
You'll find out, quit, it's too late Don't say gay, don't say black
Don't say science, don't fight back.
Don't read books, don't grow weed.
Don't you dare teach kids to think or read.
BAM like facts in a school debate.
BAM like dart they use to celebrate.
BAM like hope behind a gaze.
So crank it loud, disturb the peace.
Make dissenters call the police.
We're banded for now, why too real?
What now?
Play it louder, this song is banded for now.